Hussain Radhi Marzooq

<u>Hussain.marzooq.bh@icloud.com</u> - +971588988449 UAE – Dubai – Discovery Gardens

Professional Summery

Competent human resources professional, CIPD member and Extensively Experienced Human Resource Manager with more than 8 years' experience, in recruiting and staffing, monitoring turnover and retention, and company compliance. Desire to apply knowledge of the industry to assist in all HR related needs and strategic goals.

Multi skilled life coach with experience in dealing with people's behavior and psychology, Languages teacher, Photographer, blogger and writer.

In continues process of learning swift, IOS and web development, with the aim to learn other programing languages.

Skills

- Coaching, Leading & inspiring
- Developing
- Team work and collaborative
- Capability of fast learning and adapt to changes
- Working under pressures
- Event Management
- Ms.Office Advance
- Excel and formulas Expert

CONTACT DETAILS

Portfolio: https://immortality00.github.io/hussain.marzooq/

GitHub: https://github.com/immortality00

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/immortality00

Photography - Instagram : @The.3.eye

Work Experience

Garden Scape Landscape Contracting - HR & Admin Manager

Bahrain - April 2015 until June 2015

Handling and managing:

- The Employee Relations
- Recruitments process
- Training,
- Performance Management,
- Learning & Development
- Payroll,
- Salaries & benefits.
- HR budgets,
- Reports and Analysis.

- Creating the HR Department from the scratch
- Preparing and implementing The Policy & Procedures.

Imervs Al Zavani Fused Minerals - HR Officer

Bahrain - August 2014 until April 2015

Handling and Managing:

- The Employee Relations
- Recruitments process
- Training,
- Performance Management,
- Learning & Development
- Payroll, Salaries & benefits.
- HR budgets, Reports and Analysis
- Employees database and records

- Leading and directing the Human Resource team to deliver a comprehensive HR services
- Supporting the Managing Director in the policy & procedures preparing and implementation.

National Concrete Company - Payroll Officer & HR Coordinator

Bahrain - October 2011 To August 2014

Supporting the HR manager in:

- Budget planing,
- Recruitment process.
- MIS
- Training and development plan
- Developing the HR practices and procedures .
- Implementing new software for the company

Managing and handling:

- Payroll
- Reports
- Contracts, letters, and forms
- Monitoring and training the department team

Supporting The HR team in:

- Employees relations
- Administration
- Invoices clearances

Havelock AHI - HR Officer

Bahrain - October 2007- May 2011

Handling and maintaining:

- Payroll
- Administration / HR Reports.
- Administration / HR Budget
- All the invoices related to Administration, HR and employee fees
- Employees, details, training, files, leaves and vacations
- Immigration, Ministries, Embassies and visas, Staffs/workers transports, drivers, administration expenses.

- Coordinating with The Company Branches in GCC for all Administration/HR related.
- Assisting in events managements

Languages

Arabic & English .. Learning Russian - Very Beginner Level

Education

| Astrolab | Web Development | | Dubai | 2018 |
|---|--|-----------|----------------------|--------------|
| London Brewery | Swift & IOS Development | | Udemy – online | 2018 |
| CIPD Diploma in Human Resources Practice (| | (QCF), | UK | 2014 |
| Victory Training Institute | CIPD LVI 3 – Foundation, A Diploma in HR and L&D Personal & Professional Development Skills Throw NLP | | Bahrain | 2014 |
| Horizons HRD | | | Bahrain | 2011 |
| Bisan Institute of Hospitality Management | | | Bahrain | 2004 |
| Certificates | | | | |
| Harvest Training Center | The Art and Science of Value Based Decision Making | | Bahrain | 2014 |
| Harvest Training Center | Coaching for Effective Leadership | | Bahrain | 2014 |
| Logic Institute | Effective Business Emails | | Bahrain | 2013 |
| Additional Experie | nce | | | |
| English Teacher | CPAT Languages School | Egypt | Feb 17 – December | er 2017 |
| English Teacher | AIESEC – St Petersburg | Russia | March 2016 | |
| Life Coach & Consultant | Freelancing | Worldwide | April 2013 – Present | |
| Marshal | Bahrain Motorsports Marshal Club & Motor Federation | Bahrain | 2004 – 2010 | |
| Secretary | AL Ghadeer Graphics | Bahrain | August 2007 – Sep | otember 2007 |
| Sales Man Al Sorror Bahrain | | Bahrain | 2006 – Summer Job | |
| Customer service | Home Center – Marina Mall | Bahrain | 2006 – Summer Jo | b |
| Refrences | | | | |
| | | | | |

| Zahra AL Qassab | HR Manager | +97339002622 | Zahra.Alqassab@rma-rheinau.de |
|-----------------|----------------------|--------------|-------------------------------|
| Zainab Abdulla | HR Manager | +97333993665 | Zainab@nccbahrain.com |
| M V Raju | Sr. Business support | +97317832029 | Raju@havelockahi.biz |
| Moh'd Imran | HR Manager | +97333118679 | |